http://www.fixac.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
PRK Services, Inc. is sensitive to the private nature of information you provide to us over the Internet. Our Privacy Policy is designed to protect your personal information while at the same time giving you the opportunity to obtain interesting and useful information, products and services.
Personal information may include your name, phone number, address and e–mail address along with other information by which you can be personally identified.
We also collect usage information from you when you visit us. Web Site usage information is not identifiable information. It describes how our Web Site is used and navigated, including the number and frequency of visitors to each Web page and the length of their stay. Web Site usage information also includes the domain names of browsers that visit our Web Site, time of day the Web Site was visited and other non–personally identifiable information.
Please click here to contact us if you have any further questions about our privacy policy or to stop receiving future emails, phone calls, or other direct communications from PRK Services, Inc..
Promotions
$50 Discount on Service Repair
$49 Service Call
View all
Newsletter
Submit your email to receive promotions:
Email *
Structured Particle *
Submit
Reviews
You have all been awesome and it did not cost me an arm and leg, and apparently there is not something else I need to fix...amazed!! Kudos guys and gals!!
- Satisfied Customer
Read all
Service Area
Argyle Aubrey Corinth Denton Flower Mound Highland Village Lantana Oak Point Providence Village Trophy Club
and more
Search your Zip code below.
Leaking Ducts? You’re Losing Out on Energy!
Read More
Read all
Your
UNIVERSAL SAVINGS AGREEMENT
Which includes our "Exclusive Precision Tune-Up"
904 South Woodrow Lane,
Denton,
TX
76205-6318
940-382-8554
Office Hours
Mon-Fri 7am-4pm, Always available to take your call 24/7After Hours Service Available including weekends
License# TACLA 26542C
we accept the following payment types:
Financing Available:
Connect With Us:
Facebook
Twitter
YouTube
Google Maps
© 2012–2020 PRK Services, Inc. All rights reserved.
iMarket Solutions: Dedicated to Contractor Success
